I know, I know, what you must do is train.
Već znam, već znam, morate trenirati.
The thing about gymnastics is that you release endorphins, do you understand?
Što ima vježbanje jest da otpuštaš endorfine, razumiteš li me?
And that helps with stress relief, depression, among other things.
To je... uklanja stres i depresiju.
I mean, gymnastics really help out in so many ways.
Znači, vježbanjem možete pomoći u mnogome.
The thing is, when someone doesn't have the physical... attitude,
Problem nastaje kada ne postoji odlučnost... fizička,
when one doesn't have the willpower.
kada netko nema želju.
Tell me where I can find it because if there's somewhere selling me
Recite mi gdje mogu pronaći tu želju ili spremnost za vježbanje, jer ako postoji neki takav prostor koji bih ja mogao platiti,
willpower or the right attitude towards training, going to the gym.
da bih pronašao motivaciju ili spremnost da vježbam, da ideм i treniraм.
Oh my God, please tell me where it is because I just don't have it.
Bog moj, molim vas, recite mi gdje, jer ja sam ju izgubila.
I don't have it, I can't seem to find it, it's nowhere inside me.
Ne je sa mnom, ne mogu je pronaći, nije dio mene.
Wherever the hell I left it, assuming it exists since everyone says,
Ne znam gdje ta jebena želja moje je, ako je uopće ikad postojala, svi ti kažu da,
You start off...
Počnete...
Once you get started with the gym, you always feel like doing more.
Kada započnete vježbati, svaki put želite više.
It never happened to me before!
To mi se još nikada nije dogodilo!
I hate it! I go to the gym, work out, and come back swearing. Do you understand me?
Patnem za time! Idem u fitness centar, vježbam i dolazim bijesno. Razumiteš li me?
Because sometimes, I just don't feel like going.
Jeri drugog dana... nisam imao želje ni snage otići.
All I want to do is sit at home; I don't feel like working out.
Želim samo sjediti kod kuće, nema me želje vježbati.
What am I supposed to do, sister?
Što da učini, sestra?